<resources>
    <string name="app_name">scrollingtext</string>
    <string name="article_title">Unfinished and Unedited Story</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">Fake Heroes</string>
    <string name="article_text">
        If you liked the story consider following me here: www.google.com
        \n\n
        “There is something wrong here.” Heinz says as he takes in the situation.

Currently, the Five-Colored Blades led by Heinz were investigating a ruin that had reports of \'suspicious\' activity. The pay was good and there was likely something in there of note so the Heinz accepted the quest after the input of his team. Their ruin exploration had been uneventful until they came across a circle-shaped door.
\n\n
Edgar was currently examining the door with his skills as rouge to find a hidden mechanism.
\n\n
“Nothing.” The rouge says with a shake of his head, “It doesn\'t open from this side apparently.
\n\n
“What? But there we didn\'t see any other doors.” Delizah points out.
\n\n
Indeed, the ruin was mostly hallways. Aside from this door, they hadn\'t come across a single door or any other hidden mechanism. Perhaps, they missed something.
\n\n
Jennifer strokes her chin as a thought comes to mind, “Maybe there was a second entrance that we missed.”
\n\n
“Possibly.” Diana says as she places her hand on the door, “Or, maybe this is a tomb and they did that to deter grave robbers.”
\n\n
At that moment, the sound of moving stones echoes through dark empty halls of the ruin. Diana quickly removes her from the door as it begins to shift. The door moves back a foot or two before it turns to the right and disappears behinds the wall.
\n\n
<b>“Ah, so you figured out that an elf needs to touch the door.”</b> A smooth suave voice says.
\n\n
Immediately, the Five-Colored Blades drew their weapons and looked up to see a tall, lean figure standing on the stone slab at the far end of the room. The figure was definitely male and was dressed in clothing that a high-class steward would wear. Their hands were clad in golden gauntlets engraved with numerous symbols that no one in Heinz\'s party recognized. Their hair was short and green and had been sleeked back. However, the most noteworthy trait was the featureless white mask the figure was wearing. The mask only had holes for the eyes but nothing else.
\n\n
“You\'re…a Majin?” An unsure Heinz asks.
\n\n
All the Majin he had encountered up till now had horns, yet this man did not. However, he \'felt\' similar to a Majin. At least, that is what Heinz\'s instincts told him.
\n\n
<b>“I guess that is what I would be considered.”</b> The figure says before preforming an elegant bow, <b>“But, where are my manners? My name is Chandra, Demon Lord of Puppets, Masks, and Forgery.”</b>
\n\n
Chandra\'s chartreuse-yellow eyes at Five-Colored Blades and see that they haven\'t lowered their weapons or dropped their guards in the slightest.
\n\n
Heinz points his sword at Chandra accusingly as he shouts, “So you\'re the one causing all the trouble!”
\n\n
Chandra tilts his head to the side.
\n\n
“What trouble?” He asks, “State exactly what I did.”
\n\n
The Five-Colored Blades exchange looks. Now that they thought about it, the request never stated the exact reason and, instead, had simply put \'suspicious\' activity. It was very odd but one could assume a number of things based off of \'suspicious activity\'. It was a catch-all term in a sense.
\n\n
Heinz narrows his eyes, “You…” He starts before trailing off.
\n\n
“Yes?” Chandra places his hands behind his back and leans forward, “What did I do? Harassed humans?”
\n\n
“That\'s right! That has to be it!” Heinz says, his grip tightening on his sword, “You were definitely planning something!”
\n\n
Chandra chuckles to himself at this \'hero\'. He had seen many so-called \'heroes\' in his days. The ones before him were quite…underwhelming at best. They reminded him more of glorified mercenaries rather than heroes.
\n\n
“Is that so?” Chandra says and leans forward again, “Or, perhaps I was simply guarding this place against humans and elves who have no business being here.”
\n\n
“This is their land.” Heinz counters.
\n\n
“Wrong.” Chandra shakes his head, “Their village is their land. They don\'t own this ruin or anything inside it.” He shifts his hands from behind his back, “Is that truly your argument? If so, allow me to pose a question: if the roles were reversed, if in the villager\'s shoes and vice-versa, who would you side with?”
\n\n
Heinz narrows his eyes, “I\'d pick-”
\n\n
“The villagers.” Chandra interrupts and finishes Heinz\'s sentence, “You had your mind made up before you even arrived here. But, if you actually bothered to do some research you would know that local Maijin and the villagers have made an agreement that these ruins belong to the Maijin.”
\n\n
Heinz\'s grip on his sword tightened. Perhaps seeing this, Diana spoke up,
\n\n
“If what your saying is true then there should be documentation of that transaction?” Diana asks, “To me, that sounds like something both the Maijin and villagers would agree to sign documents to prevent future problems.”
\n\n
Chandra turns to her with his chartreuse-yellow eyes, “Indeed.” He answers with a shrug, “But, I do not have a document confirming or denying what I\'m saying.”
\n\n
“Then-”
\n\n
The green-haired Archdemon raises a clawed finger, “But, what evidence do the villagers have to confirm that no such deal occurred? Why would you trust them over me when we have the same level of credibility, and the same amount of evidence?”
\n\n
Chandra chuckled darkly.
\n\n
“If you were to ask the villagers they would deny such a document existed or that it was lost.” Chandra said as his eyes seemed to start to glow, “But, I\'d doubt that the Maijin would be so…careless with such a crucial document. Especially one that recognized their rights to pieces of land even if they\'re ruins like these.”
</string>
    <string name="add_comment">Add Comment</string>
</resources>